

- ennourhamza@gmail.com
- ★ Kowait Avenue, Hammamet
- +21624281526
- % hamzaennour.live

#### Social networks

@HamzaEnnour

in @hamza-ennour-b348311b8

# Languages

#### **Arabic**

Native language

#### **French**

Professional competence

#### **English**

Professional competence

#### **Certificats**

# Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Google Digital Garage

# Programming Foundations:

LinkedIn

# Programming Foundations: Fundamentals

LinkedIn

Succeeding in Web
Development: Full Stack and
Front End

LinkedIn

# Hamza Ennour

# Software engineer

As a computer engineer with a passion for web development, I strive to continuously enhance my skills and stay up-to-date with the latest technologies. I have had the privilege of working on some exciting projects, and I would be honored if you took a moment to explore my e-portfolio at hamzaennour.live to learn more about my experiences and capabilities.

# **Education**

**National Engineering Degree in Software Engineering** 

2016 - 2022 **ESPRIT** Ariana

Bachelor's degree in Mathematics

2015 - 2016 Mhamed Boudhina Hammamet High School Hammamet

# Work experience

# Full-Stack JS Developer (Internship)

03/2022 - 10/2022 Oodexia France

- Development of web application for monitoring candidates during online recruitment tests and detecting potential frauds.
- Technologies and tools: Nodejs v17, React.Js v16, ExpressJs, Postman, VSCode, GitHub, Firebase Cloud, Google Cloud, Google Function, ChartJs, Docker, Jira.

# Full-Stack JS Developer (Internship)

06/2021 - 09/2021 Ulysse Media Tunis

- Design and development of three mini-applications, including Fields, Club, and Site Gark.
- Implementation of sophisticated features such as field management, event creation, financial management, subscription management, and a player interface
- Technologies and tools: Nodejs v15, Angular v12, ExpressJs, MongoDB, Postman, VSCode, GitHub, Firebase Cloud, AWS, NGINX, ChartJs, Cron Schedule.

## Full-Stack JS Developer (Internship)

07/2020 - 09/2020 CFTravel Hammamet

- Rebuilding a WordPress-based website of a travel agency, using Node.js as the back-end and Vue.js as the front-end.
- Update of the appointment and hotel management on the website.
- **Technologies and tools:** Nodejs V13, VueJs V2.8, Vue Router, ExpressJs, MySql, Postman, VSCode.

# Developer (Internship)

07/2018 - 09/2018 ODD Hammamet

- Design of an interface in an Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) desktop application.
- **Technologies and tools :** Object-C, Xml, Oracle Sql,Notepad++.

#### Technical skills

# **Programming languages**

JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, Php, C, C++, C#, Python.

#### **Frameworks**

Angular, VueJs, Symfony, Laravel SpringBoot, J2EE,ExpressJs, .NET, Django.

#### Libraries

React.js, JQuery, Ajax.

# **Runtime environment**

Node.js, JRE. Base de données MySQL, PL/SQL, MongoDB, Oracle.

## **Deployment**

AWS, Heroku, OVH, Vercel, Firebase, Google Cloud.

#### Other

HTML, CSS, Sass, BootStrap, GIT, Scrum, UX/UI Design, UML.

#### **Personal Skills**

Creativity Efficiency Project Management Teamwork Problem Solving

#### **Interests**

Artificial intelligence Football Gaming

# **Personal Projects**

# Microservice Project

09/2021 - 11/2021

- Restructuring the architecture of an established e-commerce project into microservices, aimed at boosting performance and integrating novel features such as online payment, promotions, and human resource management. (Collaborative project with two freelancers)
- **Technologies and tools :** SpringBoot, Nodejs v14, ExpressJs, Angular v12, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, MySql, Api Gateway, Eureka, Heroku, Docker, Postman, VSCode, GitHub.

## Closer (Smart Virtual Classroom)

02/2021 - 06/2021

- Development of a collaborative video conferencing tool with an online White Board, meeting rooms, and screen sharing capabilities for teachers and tutors looking to organize highly interactive and real-time online teaching sessions. (Team project)
- **Technologies and tools :** Node.js v14, React.js v15, Express.js, MongoDB, Postman, VSCode, GitHub, Firebase Cloud, WebRTC, PeerJs, authentification oauth2.

### Lux Queen

10/2020 - 12/2020

- Design and development of the front-end part of an e-commerce project dedicated to the sale of cosmetics and personal care products.

  Implementation of a JSON server as a backend. Creation of an intuitive and user-friendly interface to facilitate the online shopping experience.
- **Technologies and tools**: Angular 9, JSON-server, Bootstrap, Github, Vscode.

#### EdTech (school management system)

01/2019 - 06/2019

- Creation of a multi-platform application (Desktop/Web/Mobile) for managing the school system of a private school, allowing for course supervision and giving parents the ability to follow their children's progress.
- **Technologies and tools :** Symfony, JavaFX, CodeName One, Javascript, Mysql, Vscode, Github, Trello, Scrum, Slack.

# Project for a restaurant

04/2021 - 11/2021

- Development of a restaurant owner dashboard, account management, product and category management, integration of an online payment system, and complaint management on the first platform.
- Design and implementation of the second platform, enabling customers to order and pay online and communicate with the delivery person via a chat feature. (Collaborative project with four freelancers)
- **Technologies and tools :** Nodejs v14, Expressjs, NextJs v13, Tailwindcss, Redux, ReactJs v15, AWS, Firebase,Trello, Scrum, Slack.

#### Kaadam (project for students and businesses owners)

03/2021 - 07/2021

- Development of a web application that enables a company to recruit students for specific tasks within projects.
- Implementation of features such as managing teams, missions, contracts, and task assignment process.
- Technologies and tools: SpringBoot, Angular v12, Postman, Mysql, VS Code, Firebase, Spring Security, Docker